BRAC Chicago Files 5488 A
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Charges Against Officers - Division 57, 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Charges Against Officers - Division 58, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Charges Against Officers - Division 88, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Charges Against Officers - Suspension of E.J. Carey GC Division 98, Illegal Agreement, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Subordinate Divisions - General, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Audits - Subordinate Divisions and Grand, 1958-1969 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Loans and Financial Assistance to Subordinate Divisions, 1956-1970 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- ORT-AFL Chapter, 1945-1967 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Charter Applications, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Charters to be Relinquished, 1936-1968 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Elections-Subordinate Divisions-General Correspondence, 1960-1972 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Interpretation - Labor Management Reporting and Disclosure Act as applies to Elections, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Quadrennial Elections - General Correspondence, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Emblem and Seal, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Waiving dues - General, 1961-1969 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Withdrawal Cards-45 Year Cards-Life Member Cards, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Funds - General, 1952-1970 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Protective Fund - Various Expenses, 1963-1969 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Welfare Fund - Established 1927 Convention, 1961-1970 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Disaster Fund - BRAC, 1969-1971 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- R.C.B.U. - Railway Clerks for a Better Union, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Fund - Convention, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Special Assessments-General-Samples Various Policies on Waiving or Collecting Members Assessments, 1963-1968 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Special Assessments Levied by Grand Division - Record of all Assessments Levied (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Protective Fund - Special Assessments, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Issued 5-20-68
- Special Assessment - Protective Fund, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  Issued 6-1-67
- Florida East Coast Special Assessments, 1963-1966 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Special Assessments levied by Divisions - Record of All Assessments Levied by Division, 1946-1969 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Special Assessment - NY Central System, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Special Assessment - Seaboard Coast Line, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- By-Laws - Dues - Salaries - General, 1969-1971 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Dues - Membership - Revenues - Salaries, 1961-1969 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Salaries - Dues, By-Laws Changes in Dues Initiation Fees Subsequent 1968 Convention, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Comparisons Dues Rate and Hourly Wages (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Convention General Correspondence, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Convention - Merger Committee, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Convention Sentinels and Committees, 1968-1971 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Grievances and Appeals Committee, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Credential Committee, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Committee on Committees, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Convention BRAC and T-C, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Trans Communicator - General Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Printing - Contract and Bids, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Advertising - Contract and Bids, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Trans Communicator Current Year, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Membership Circulation - Report by State, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Educational Bureau, ORT, General, 1964-1968 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Copyright Station Agents Blue Book, 1947-1958 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Printing - Contract and Bids Station and Agent Blue Books, 1948-1961 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Educational Matters Pertaining to Labor, 1965-1969 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Education Classes - TCU General Officers, 1960-1966 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- BRAC Job Corps, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Telegraph Schools, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Federal Agencies - General, 1967-1971 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- U.S. Department of Labor - General, 1963-1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- U.S. Savings Bonds - General, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- U.S. Department of Transportation - General Correspondence, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Federal Laws and Regulations - General, 1961-1967 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Laws Affecting Railroad Telegraphers in USA and Canada - Mr. Joslin's Book, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  10/1/1969
- Executive Orders, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Executive Order 11491 Federal Government Employees Right To Organize, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Taxes - General, 1956-1969 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Exemption From Income Tax Reports from M-0284, 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Job Abolishments as result of Railpax-Amtrack, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Railpax - National Railraod Passenger Corporation, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Price - Wage Freeze, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Civil Rights - General Correspondence, 1959-1969 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Civil Service Classification Law, 1944-1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Canadian Fair Employment Practices Act, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Communism - General Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Federal Hours of Service Act, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Federal and State Workmen's Compensation Laws - Federal Employees Liability Act, 1957-1965 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Canadian Workmen's Compensation Act, 1957-1965 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Immigration Laws, 1953-1969 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Welfare and Pension plans Disclosure Act, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Welfare and Pension Plaans Disclosure Act 1958 - Bonding Requirements, 1961-1966 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Taft Hartley Act, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Fair Labor Standards Act 1938 - Wage and Hour, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- National Labor Relations Act - Amendments - NLRB Decisions General Correspondence, 1936-1961 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Corporations and Labor Unions Returns Act - Canada, 1961-1965 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Canada Labour (Standards) Code - Re Hours - Minimum Wages - Vacations and Holidays, 1964-1969 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Urban Mass Transportation Act of 1964, 1962-1972 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- High Speed Ground Transportation Research and Development Act of 1965, 1965-1968 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Public Law 89-485, 1964-1966 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  Signed by President 7/1/66 Amend Bank Holding Act
- Maintenance of Railway Operation Act - Canada, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Pension Benefits Standards Act - Canada, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Public Law 90-54 Est. SPEC-BD for settlement of shop craft disputes (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Public Law 90-202 Age Discrimination Employment Act, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Universal Military Training and Services Act - General, 1943-1971 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Universal Military Training and Services Act and Amendments, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Rights of Returning Veterans - Pamphlets - interpretation of Proposed Memo Agreement, 1947-1969 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Canadian Veterans Benefit Act - General, 1949-1955 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Labor Management 2 and 3, 1968-1971 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Labor Management Reporting and Disclosures Act 1959 - General Correspondence, 1959-1965 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Landrum-Griffin Act Analysis - E.J. Hickey, Jr. ORT and other organizations (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Landrum-Griffin Act Analysis - NYU, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  Apr-68
- Decisions of E.J. Hickey, Jr. on Labor Management Reporting and disclosures Act of 1959, 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Investigations under Labor Management Reporting and Disclosure Act, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Extra Coppies Explanatory Booklets - Bur. Labor Management Reports, 1960-1968 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Labor Management Reporting and Disclosure Act - Reporting Forms and Instructions, 1959-1964 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Labor Management Reporting and Disclosure Act - Bonding Requirements, 1959-1966 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Transportation Act of 1920 and Amendments, 1958-1972 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- State Laws - General, 1959-1968 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- State Laws - Alabama, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- State Laws - Arizona, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- State Laws - Arkansas, 1961-1968 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- State Laws - California, 1960-1968 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- State Laws - Colorado (Box 19, Folder 20)
- State Laws - Florida, 1960-1969 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- State Laws - Georgia, 1958-1969 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- State Laws - Idaho (Box 20, Folder 2)
- State Laws - Illinois, 1961-1968 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- State Laws - Indiana, 1961-1969 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- State Laws - Iowa, 1959-1969 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- State Laws - Kansas, 1959-1967 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- State Laws - Kentucky, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- State Laws - Louisiana (Box 20, Folder 8)
- State Laws - Michigan, 1964-1969 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- State Laws - Minnesota, 1961-1963 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- State Laws - Mississipi, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- State Laws - Missouri, 1951-1958 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- State Laws - Montana, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- State Laws - Nebraska, 1959-1969 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- State Laws - Nevada, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- State Laws - New Jersey, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- State Laws - New Mexico (Box 20, Folder 17)
- State Laws - New York, 1956-1965 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- State Laws - North Dakota, 1936-1960 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- State Laws - Ohio, 1960-1965 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- State Laws - Oklahoma, 1962-1969 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- State Laws - Oregon (Box 20, Folder 22)
- State Laws - Pennsylvania, 1957-1968 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- State Laws - South Carolina, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- State LAws - South Dakota, 1957-1967 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- State Laws - Tennessee, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- State Laws - Texas, 1960-1966 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- State Laws - Utah (Box 20, Folder 28)
- State Laws - Vermont, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- State Laws - Virginia (Box 20, Folder 30)
- State Laws - Washington (Box 20, Folder 31)
- State Laws - West Virginia, 1963-1969 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- State Laws - Wisconsin, 1950-1968 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Canadian Provincial Laws and Regulations, 1960-1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Canadian Provincial Laws and Regulations - Newfoundland, 1959-1967 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Registration Trade Unions Act - Newfoundland, 1960-1964 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Political - General Correspondence, 1964-1970 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Political Endorsements, 1968-1970 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Government Officials - Senators and Representatives, 1961-1967 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Congressional Voting Records, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- COPE - AFL-CIO, 1960-1969 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- TCU Political League - General, 1966-1968 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- TCU Political League - Contributions, 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Alabama, 1960-1971 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Alaska (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Arizona, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Arkansas, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- California, 1967-1971 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Colorado (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Connecticut, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Delaware, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- District of Columbia (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Florida, 1966-1970 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Georgia, 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Idaho, 1966-1971 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Illinois, 1970-1972 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Indiana, 1976-1971 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Iowa (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Kansas, 1969-1972 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Kentucky, 1966-1968 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Louisiana, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Maine, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Maryland, 1965-1971 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Massachusetts, 1964-1971 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Michigan, 1966-1971 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Minnesota (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Mississippi (Box 21, Folder 34)
- Missouri, 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 35)
- Montana, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 36)
- Nebraska, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 37)
- Nevada, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 38)
- New Hampshire (Box 21, Folder 39)
- New Jersey', 1967-1971 (Box 21, Folder 40)
- New Mexico (Box 21, Folder 41)
- New York, 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 42)
- North Carolina, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 43)
- North Dakota, 1962-1966 (Box 21, Folder 44)
- Ohio, 1964-1971 (Box 21, Folder 45)
- Oklahoma, 1966-1972 (Box 21, Folder 46)
- Oregon, 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 47)
- Pennsylvania, 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 48)
- Rhode Island, 1966-1971 (Box 21, Folder 49)
- South Carolina, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 50)
- South Dakota, 1966-1971 (Box 21, Folder 51)
- Tennessee, 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 52)
- Texas, 1964-1968 (Box 21, Folder 53)
- Utah, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 54)
- Vermont, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 55)
- Virginia, 1966-1968 (Box 21, Folder 56)
- Washington, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 57)
- West Virginia (Box 21, Folder 58)
- Wisconsin, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 59)
- Wyoming (Box 21, Folder 60)
- House and Senate Bills in Numerical Order, 1961-1971 (Box 21, Folder 61)
- Proposed National Legislation, 1966-1970 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Legislation, Canadian - General Correspondence, 1960-1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Supreme Court Decision #29 - UTU and Det. and Toledo Shore Line Status Quo, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Supreme and Lower Court Decisions, 1947-1970 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Equal Employment Opportunity Civil Actions - Various Railroads and Organizations, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Automobile - Use, Mileage, etc, 1959-1968 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Carrying US Mail, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Daylight Saving Time, 1953-1968 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Dead Head Rule (Carriers Having Same), 1962-1968 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Discipline Investigations-Rules and Procedures, 1952-1966 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Drawbridges, 1955-1965 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Examinations - Rules, 1963-1967 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Examinations - Physical, 1959-1966 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Jury Duty, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Pass Regulations - US and Canada, 1958-1965 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Pumps, etc.,Rules, Meal Hour, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Sick Leave - General Correspondence, 1945-1967 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Sick Leave - Negotiating Material Agreements, Miscellaneous, 1966-1971 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Strikes - Various, Rules Movements, Division Calls, Instructions, 1959-1971 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Strike Instructions - Canada, 1950-1958 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Starting Time Rule - General, 1963-1964 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Compensation for posting - Towerman, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Student Rates, 1957-1969 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Western Union - General, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Wire Chiefs - General, 1956-1968 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Grand Division: Headquarters - General Correspondence, 1964-1971 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Duties and Responsibilities of Employees Represented by ORT, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Employment - Telegraphers Requesting, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Centralized Traffic Control - General Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Railway Express - General, 1956-1971 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Railway Express Agreements, 1934-1968 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Piggyback Service - General Correspondence, 1959-1966 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Piggyback Service - General, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Health and Welfare Plans - Other Organizations, 1958-1963 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Construction Association Hospitalization - Railroad Employees in Kentucky HB 248 General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Death Benefit - Coverage Grand - General Staff - Employees, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Group Insurance Protection for Employees transported by Company vehicle or while using privately owned vehicle in Company service, 1962- 1967 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Equitable Life Assurance Society Policy #5555 Paid by Employee (optional) - General Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Group Accident Insurance - Hospital Monthly Plan, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Travelers Accidental Death and Dismemberment Insurance Policy GA-664599 24 Hour Around the Clock Coverage, 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Provident Group Life Accidental Death and Dismemberment Policy R-166-L (paid by BRAC-commensurate with salary) - General Correspondence, 1964-1971 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Atlantic Coast Line Railroad - Provident Life and Accident Insurance, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Atlanta and West Point Railroad - Provident Life and Accident Insurance (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Provident Life and Accident Insurance Company - Group Disability Policy R-375 SP(T&L Lines), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Provident Life and Accident Insurance Company - Group Policy R-375 - Annual Report under Federal Welfare and Pension plans Disclosure Act, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Provident Life and Accident Insurance Company Group Disability Policy SP (T&L) - General Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- US Steel Plan, 1951-1966 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Bessemer and Lake Erie Railroad Health and Welfare - Steel Plan, 1956-1963 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern Railway Health and Welfare Steel Plan, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range Health and Welfare - Steel Plan, 1959-1967 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Health and Welfare: Canada - General Correspondence, 1959-1971 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Canadian Employee Benefit Plan - General Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Quebec Hospital Service Association, 1957-1961 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- The Great Western Life Assurance Company and CU Pacific Great Eastern Health and Welfare Plan, 1956-1965 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Newfoundland Health and Welfare Plan - Newfoundland Distributive Benefit Plan (Atlantic Region Canadian Railway), 1857- 1858 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Reciprocal Agreement - GA-23000 and Canadian Health and Welfare Plans, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Manitoba and Ontario Hospital Plan GA-23000 - Coordination of Events, 1958-1969 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Sun Life Assurance of Canada - Saskatchewan Health and Welfare Plan, 1957-1961 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Sun Life Assurance Company - Policy 7030-G and Amendments, 1956-1970 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Health and Welfare - General, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Contract GA-23000 - Amendments (Box 25, Folder 1)
- GA-23000 Coverage Under British Columbia Medical Service Act, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- BRAC Analysis of Claims under GA-23000, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Assessments - 1968 Health and Welfare Joint Group Policies (Box 25, Folder 4)
  revised 3/1/68
- GA-23000 - Index of Riders and Amendments from Inception, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Samples and Extra copies - Powers of Attorney, Joint Application Coverage, Termination Hospital Association and coverage by travel or other Insurance, Section 6 Notice, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Coordination of Benefits GA-23000 - General Correspondence (Payment Differnce Only When 2 Policies Carried), 1964-1968 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Conversion to Group Life Insurance, 1961-1963 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Travelers Meetings - Pen Notes of Yearly Travelers' Meetings, 1964-1968 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Interpretations of Coverage GA-23000 under various situations, 1961-1968 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Contract GA-23000 - Explanatory Booklet Notices of Claims, Other Forms, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Veteran Administration Hospital - Payment to, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Reinsurers - GA 23000. 23111. 107300, 107300L, 1963-1971 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- On-The-Job Injuries GA 230000, 1953-1957 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Health and Welfare - Christian Science Practitioner Coverage, 1955-1958 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Carrier and Employee Committee to Discuss disputes arising under Health and Welfare, 1961-1968 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Exhibits A-B-C-D-E and Supplements, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  Effective 3/1/68
- SPL Acct. Agreement - Premium Adjustment - Experience - Agreement and Amendments, 1955-1969 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  1/18/1955
- SPL Acct. Agreement - Premium Adjustment Experience - General Correspondence, 1961-1968 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Medicare - Social Security and Railroad Retirement Financed Health and Welfare Plan, 1963-1969 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- GA-23111 Health and Welfare Retired, Furloughed, Dependent Coverage - General Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Contract GA-23111 - Policy, 1959-1968 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- GA-23111 Explanatory Booklet, Notice of Claims, Other Forms, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Agreement and Amendments - Payment to Travelers and SPL.Account GA-23111, 1961-1969 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  3/1/1961
- GA-23111 - Experience - Premium Adjustment and Special Account, 1955-1971 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Status of Furloughed Employees under GA-23111 (In Division Order), 1962-1969 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- GA-23111 - Comparison Benefits with Management Plans, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Hospital Association Roads - Dependent coverage under GA-23111, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Board of Directors Approval of GA-107300 Coverage, 1955-1963 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Travelers Contract GA-107300 - General Correspondence, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Contract GA-107300 - Explanatory Booklet; Notices of Claims; Identification Cards, 1955-1966 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- GA-107300 Travelers Group Policy - Policy and Subsequent Riders, 1956-1969 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Travelers Contract GA 107300 Retired Employees Amendment G328807, 1957-1969 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  Effective 5/26/64
- Manitoba - Ontario - Quebec Hospital Insurance Plans as related to GA-107300, 1958-1969 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Medicare Refunds GA107300, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Payment to Travelers GA107300, 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- GA-107300 SPL. Account - Premium Adjustment Experience Agreements and Subsequent Changes Since July 1955, 1955- 1961 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- GA-107300 SPL. Account - Premium Adjustment-Experience - General Correspondence, 1957-1961 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- G.E. Leighty - GA 107300 Payment Hospitalization Accident, 1961-1963 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  5/21/61 and other hospitalization
- Board of Directors GA-107300, G-107300L, 1960-1962 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Office Employees GA-107300, G107300L, 1955-1967 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Staff GA-107300, G-107300L, 1955-1969 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Contract GA-107300L and Amendments, 1964-1971 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- G-107300 Life Insurance Officers and Office Employees -General Correspondence, 1959-1969 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  Revised 3/1/68
- G-107300L SPL. Acct. - Premium Adjustment Experience Life Insurance Officers and Office Employees Agreement, 1961-1968 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- G-107300L SPL. Acct. - Premium Adjustment Experience Life Insurance Officers and Office Employees - General Correspondence, 1965- 1968 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- President, Grand Secretary, Vice President GA-107300, G-107300L, 1955-1966 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Hospital Associations - General Correpondence, 1958-1969 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Assoc. Railroad Medical Service Executives - General Correpondence and REPORTER, 1952-1969 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Extension under Railroad Retirement and Railroad Unemployment Insurance Acts - Status Pass Privledges (Box 27, Folder 6)
- List Hospital Associations - Locations - Dues - History, 1949-1967 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Port Terminal Railraod Association, Employees' Hospital Association, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Galveston Wharves Hospitalization Fund, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- North East Oklahoma Railraod Company Hospital Association, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Sand Springs Hospital Association, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Texas City Hospital Association, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Gulf, Colorado and Santa Fe - Hospital Association, 1963-1969 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Linemen-General, 1919-1957 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Radio - General, 1951-1972 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Radio: Canada - General, 1945-1957 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Accident Reports - Radio Equipped Trains, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Federal and State Laws Governing use of Radio, 1958-1970 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Teletype - IBM - IDP General Correspondence, 1947-1967 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- R.E. Bridges Union Shop Arbitration Award - Norfolk and West Division 26, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Port Authority Transportation - Hudson ARB.A-49 Non-Compliance US Agreement - Dennis Laddem, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Norfolk and Western ARB.A-48 - Non-Compliance with US Agreement not paying dues first half, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Membership Survey - Delinquency, 1952-1968 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Right To Work Laws - General Correspondence, 1956-1968 (Box 27, Folder 24)